Guide to the Cornwall Miscellanea 1779-2003 MS 011 MS 011 MS 011
Cornwall Historical Society
- People
  - Benedict Family
    - Envelope that formerly contained a deed from Elizabeth Benedict to Silas Benedict, deed missing, 1817 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Deeds by which Elizabeth Bennett came into possession of the former Fennell Farm, 1821-1835 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Deed for a change in the road leading through the former Fennell Farm, 1824 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Cemetery Association Constitution, likely owned by Elizabeth Benedict, 1869 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Deeds from Cornwell family to Nathan Benedict, 1789 (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
    - Probate inventories of Nathan Benedict and Elizabeth Benedict, 1824-1870 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr from Ralph Benedict, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Beers Family
    - Portrait of Victory C. Beers, 1870 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Portion of Silas Beers’ will, 1892 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Autograph of Ralph S. Beers, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence between Victory C. Beers and E.C. Starr, 1909-1919 (Box 2, Folder 6-May)
    - Genealogical manuscript, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Beach Family
    - Genealogical letter sent to E.C. Starr, 1909 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Allen Family
    - Pennsylvania Packet account of Ethan Allen’s captivity, 1779 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Deed from Elijah Allen to Levi Pierce, 1782 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Deed from Isaac Pierce to Elijah Allen, 1783 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Deed from Seth Pierce to Elijah Allen, 1795 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Deeds from William Kellogg to Elijah Allen, 1796 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Survey for dividing parishes, by Elijah Allen, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Copy of Daniel Allen’s Revolutionary War diary, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence with E.C. Starr, regarding Daniel Allen, 1897-1901 (Box 1, Folder 12-Nov)
    - Secondary publications regarding Ethan Allen, 1849-1934; , undated (Box 1, Folder 13-26)
    - E.C. Starr correspondence, regarding Ethan Allen, 1911-1918; , undated (Box 1, Folder 27-31)
    - Sketch and portrait of Ira Allen in The American Monthly, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - E.C. Starr correspondence and notes, regarding Ira Allen, 1896-1921; , undated (Box 1, Folder 33-36)
  - Swami Abhedananda
    - Published circulars, 1914-1915; , undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Letter sent to E.C. Starr, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper article, regarding views on World War I, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Town Materials
  - Meeting Minutes, 1745-1875, with gaps (Box 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1871-1975 (Box 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1977-2015, with gaps (Box 10)
- Books and Miscellanea
  - Textbooks and Children's books (Box 11-12)
  - Textbooks, Children's books, and Religious books (Box 13)
  - Religious and Lay books (Box 14)